Guide to the Records of the New York University Photo Bureau RG 7.2.2
New York University Archives
- Unprocessed Negatives, undated
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 481)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 482)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 483)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 484)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 485)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 486)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 487)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 488)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 489)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 490)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 491)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 492)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 493)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 494)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 495)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 496)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 497)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 498)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 499)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 500)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 501)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 502)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 503)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 504)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 505)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 506)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 507)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 508)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 509)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 510)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 511)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 512)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 513)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 514)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 515)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 516)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 517)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 518)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 519)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 520)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 521)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 522)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 523)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 524)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 525)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 526)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 527)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 528)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 529)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 530)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 531)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 532)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 533)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 534)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 535)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 536)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 537)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 538)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 539)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 540)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 541)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 542)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 543)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 544)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 545)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 546)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 547)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 548)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 549)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 550)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 551)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 552)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 553)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 554)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 555)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 556)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 557)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 558)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 559)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 560)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 561)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 562)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 563)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 564)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 565)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 566)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 567)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 568a)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 569)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 570)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 571)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 572)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 573)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 574)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 575)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 576)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 577)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 578)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 579)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 580)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 581)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 582)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 583)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 584)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 585)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 586)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 587)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 588)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 589)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 590)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 591)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 592)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 593)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 594)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 595)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 596)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 597)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 598)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 599)
  - Unprocessed Negatives, undated (Box 568b)
  - Unprocessed Negatives (Box 478b, Box 478c, Box 478d, Box 478e, Box 478f, Box 478g)
- Unprocessed Flat Files
  - Unprocessed (Box 604, Box 605, Box 610, Box 611, Box 612, Box 614)
  - Study Abroad, People, Student Life (Box 606, Box 607)
  - Misc., Student Life, People (Box 608, Box 609)
  - CAS, SOE, Artwork, Illustrations (Box 613, Box 616)
  - Dental Albums (Box 615)